so
good afternoon everyone and now it's
finally time for our question fourth
uh question number four of the day so
due to an
error uh due to an error we could not
discuss the previous question correctly
but it's all right
uh we all are really sorry for that but
anyways
uh let's continue with our next question
so good afternoon everyone i am adrika
and now uh it's finally time for our
question fourth
of day fourth so uh let's start
so uh so
in a steep turn the vehicle in front
uh the vehicle in front is moving
unnecessarily
slow to overtake that vehicle
you will a shift lanes
and overtake at the curve b
will honk see wait for a straight road
to overtake
[Music]
um
so so you know these
are questions which are coming every day
we are having five questions
and by just answering these questions we
can learn a lot
uh as we all are aware that millions of
us
drive on indian roads every day and 415
people
they died because of road crashes
so it is really sad that you know all of
us are using
roads but still it is not the safest
means of transport
still it is very dangerous to be on the
roads
and and just by answering this question
uh you know we gain some knowledge
we gain some ups that what we can do
to make sure that lesser people die
because of road crashes
so uh so as our campaign
just by simply uh just by simply
answering this
small question you can become a part of
it
uh you know you will become a part of it
and you can save
many lives also on the roads and
you know there are really a lot of
benefits
first is that you will learn about it
you will gain awareness that how our
behavior should be there
uh so we will learn a lot uh you know we
will
first of all we will learn that how our
behavior should be there
on the roads the second thing is
yeah so uh so the second thing is that
we will save millions of lives you know
of
all these peoples who die they because
uh they die because people they do not
follow traffic rules
they do not know about road safety so
the second
thing is that we can save many lives
and then what else uh will happen
just by answering this simple question
you can win
some exclusive prizes uh
just by simply answering these questions
either a bike safety kit for you and
your family
or a car safety kit so just think about
that
by such a simple step we will learn a
lot we will
uh we will save many lives and we can
also win some prizes and
this is just and this all you know we
can gain
just by simply answering this small
question
uh so i'll once again repeat it so in a
steep
turn the vehicle in front is moving
unnecessarily slow to overtake the
vehicle
you will a shift lanes and overtake at
the curve
b will honk c
wait for a straight road to overtake d
flash your lights so it is uh you know
just by answering this simple question
we can learn a lot we can win prizes and
we can save many lives also
and it is really simple to answer this
also
either you can answer this question with
the link in the description
uh with with the help of that link you
can answer
or you can also answer this from
our youtube page or from our facebook
page
so uh you know every two hours we will
be getting questions like these
uh like it uh like the question which we
are discussing right now it is the
fourth question of day four
so the same way we will be getting
uh new questions also so these questions
uh we are having five questions each day
on the gap of two hours and each
question is valid
for two hours like this question which
we are discussing right now it is also
valid for two hours and then after
these two hours our next question will
come
so uh so you know we will get multiple
questions we will get five questions
every day and in total if we talk
if we count all the questions then in
total we have 75
questions which we will be discussing uh
in
a in a in a time period of a few days
uh which we will be discussing and you
all will be answering
so you know we can see that
how simple it is like
just for answering a question it does
not take a lot of time also
minimum maximum it will take two minutes
to simply answer this
so so it is really simple we just have
to answer this question
and then we have to wait for the results
the results
uh will be announced at 10 pm every day
the results will be announced at 10 pm
we have a show called bluntly speaking
which comes
every day at 10 pm so in that show
the results will be announced so
as we discussed that you know millions
of
lives are lost because of road crashes
every day
and uh and by just by answering the
simple question
we are learning that why it is important
uh to follow all the traffic rules and
just like we uh we learn and then we
we just apply whatever we have learned
in our lives
so the same way uh the question which we
are answering right now
when we will get the results we will
learn from the
from the results and then we will know
that
how we should be acting you know how our
behavior should be there
uh in such situations like
all these questions they are based uh
based on road safety only that
uh that what we can do in certain
situations
what we can do in different types of
like uh the question which we are
discussing right now
it is if you are in us if in a steep
turn the vehicle in front of you it is
moving unnecessarily slow
and you have to overtake it then what
will you do
in such situation so
so uh with this campaign we also learned
that
why is it important to follow traffic
rules and why it is important to know
about
road safety uh many people like
it is observed that uh if we just take a
small example
of helmets that people via helmets
uh only when they see a traffic police
for children
but we must understand that that all
this road safety awareness
all these traffic rules they are for our
own
safety and hence we should not be
following them
for challan but we should be following
them
uh we shall be following them we should
be obeying them
for our own life you know they can save
our
own life so what we should be doing is
that we should be following all these
traffic rules
all these road safety rules because
they are for our own life so
i will request you all to become a part
of this
answer this question and also answer the
next questions which will be coming
uh today as well as tomorrow i will be
requesting all of you to answer them as
well
because by with by answering each
question
we can learn a lot
so with this simple step of answering a
question
we can learn a lot and
we can be a part of this uh so i will
once again summarize
this uh this question so in a steep
turn the vehicle in front is moving
unnecessarily slow and
to over that to overtake
that vehicle uh what will you do so
a shift lanes and overtake at the curve
b will honk see wait for a straight road
to overtake
or d flash your lights so
so uh as we see that with this simple
step of answering this question
we can win prizes we can get awareness
as well as we can also uh as well as we
can
also uh save many lives
of people who are dying on
indian roads every day because of
road crashes so i will request all of
you to become a part of this
uh by answering these questions and
also to ask other people also
to come and join this campaign uh
to come and answer these questions
you can ask your family you can tell
your friends about it
so that they also get this awareness
uh because uh because you know our roads
will not change when only one person
will change
everybody has to change and to
bring that change uh you know we all can
tell our family we all can tell our
friends about this
that what we should do uh what
uh how we can save many lives
how we can win some prizes also
so you know we can uh just buy this
small step we can win some prizes
every day either a bike safety kit or
a car safety kit so uh
so to win this you know we have a lot of
questions which you can answer
uh every two hours a new question will
come
every day there are five uh questions
and
every two hours each question will be
coming
uh like uh like right now it is
three o'clock so the next question will
come
in next two hours which is question
number fifth
so like this uh we can
answer these questions and also when
uh win some prizes uh you know it is
really simple to answer them
uh either we can answer them with the
help of the link
in the description uh in the description
or we can also answer them or you can
also answer them
uh from our youtube page or from our
facebook page the results as i just
talked about
the results uh you can get in our
show called bluntly speaking which comes
at 10 pm
every day we will be announcing the
results as well as the answers
uh in that show and also the results
will be shown
on our web page as well uh you know joey
how many answers
uh we can do this so
i will request all of you to please
[Music]
so ah so you know just by answering this
simple step
uh this simple question just by
answering this
simple question just by taking this
small step
we can learn a lot we can create
awareness
and we can win some prizes
so i will discuss the question once
again
so in a steep turn the vehicle in front
is moving unnecessarily slow to over
that
to overtake that vehicle you will
a shift lanes and overtake at the curve
b will honk c wait
for a straight road to overtake d
flash your lights so this is the
question
and uh i request all of you to please
answer this question and become a part
of it
and also answer the next questions as
well
and each question is valid for two hours
uh so you have only two hours for
answering this question
so uh so i will request all of you to
please
take part in this uh and also take part
in the
other questions which will be coming
next next
as well so thank you so much everyone
uh thank you so much everyone uh for
becoming
a part and please answer this because
uh you know
[Music]
just by this simple step we can learn
a lot thank you so much everyone